<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Unshell</title>
  
  
  <link href="/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://unshell.github.io/blog/"/>
  <updated>2019-11-25T08:55:56.250Z</updated>
  <id>https://unshell.github.io/blog/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Unshell</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>MarkDown 语法及样式</title>
    <link href="https://unshell.github.io/blog/2019/11/25/MarkDown%20%E8%AF%AD%E6%B3%95%E5%8F%8A%E6%A0%B7%E5%BC%8F/"/>
    <id>https://unshell.github.io/blog/2019/11/25/MarkDown%20%E8%AF%AD%E6%B3%95%E5%8F%8A%E6%A0%B7%E5%BC%8F/</id>
    <published>2019-11-25T07:55:21.532Z</published>
    <updated>2019-11-25T08:55:56.250Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="文字"><a href="#文字" class="headerlink" title="文字"></a>文字</h3><p><em>斜体文字</em></p><p><strong>粗体文字</strong></p><p><strong><em>粗斜体文字</em></strong></p><p><code>重点文字</code></p><p><del>删除文字</del></p><p><u>下划线</u></p><h3 id="列表"><a href="#列表" class="headerlink" title="列表"></a>列表</h3><ul><li>第一项</li><li>第二项</li></ul><ol><li>第一项：<ul><li>嵌套一</li></ul></li><li>第二项<ul><li>嵌套二</li></ul></li></ol><h3 id="区块"><a href="#区块" class="headerlink" title="区块"></a>区块</h3><blockquote><p>区块一级</p><blockquote><p>区块二级</p></blockquote></blockquote><h3 id="代码"><a href="#代码" class="headerlink" title="代码"></a>代码</h3><figure class="highlight java"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line"><span class="keyword">var</span> str = <span class="string">"hello world"</span>;</span><br><span class="line">System.out.print(str);</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><h3 id="链接"><a href="#链接" class="headerlink" title="链接"></a>链接</h3><ul><li><p>图片链接:<img src="/blog/favicon.png" alt="图片链接"></p></li><li><p>跳转链接：<a href="https://github.com/unshell" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://github.com/unshell</a></p></li></ul><h3 id="表格"><a href="#表格" class="headerlink" title="表格"></a>表格</h3><table><thead><tr><th align="left">表格标题1</th><th align="left">表格标题2</th><th align="left">表格标题3</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td align="left">表格内容1</td><td align="left">表格内容2</td><td align="left">表格内容3</td></tr></tbody></table><h3 id="支持-HTML-元素"><a href="#支持-HTML-元素" class="headerlink" title="支持 HTML 元素"></a>支持 HTML 元素</h3><p>列如： <kbd>Ctrl</kbd> + <kbd>C</kbd> 复制</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      MarkDown 对该主题的样式展示
    
    </summary>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Human Hair Behind Pigeons&#39; Lost Toes, Paris Study Finds</title>
    <link href="https://unshell.github.io/blog/2019/11/25/Essay-03/"/>
    <id>https://unshell.github.io/blog/2019/11/25/Essay-03/</id>
    <published>2019-11-25T06:17:03.160Z</published>
    <updated>2019-11-25T08:54:32.904Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>文章译文仅供参考</p></blockquote><h3 id="Part-1"><a href="#Part-1" class="headerlink" title="Part 1"></a>Part 1</h3><p>For a long time scientists thought the fact that pigeons in urban environments often lost their toes was due to some form of infection, or was a reaction to chemical pollutants. </p><p>长期以来，科学家认为，城市环境中的鸽子经常失去脚趾是由于某种形式的感染，或者是对化学污染物的反应。</p><h3 id="Part-2"><a href="#Part-2" class="headerlink" title="Part 2"></a>Part 2</h3><p>But now researchers in France believe they’ve stumbled upon the real culprit: human hair.</p><p>但是现在法国的研究人员相信他们偶然发现了真正的罪魁祸首：人类的头发。</p><h3 id="Part-3"><a href="#Part-3" class="headerlink" title="Part 3"></a>Part 3</h3><p>The team from the National Museum of Natural History and the University of Lyon recorded the occurrence and extent of toe mutilations from pigeons eking out their time in 46 sites across Paris.</p><p>来自里昂大学和国家自然历史博物馆的研究团队找到了生活在巴黎46个地点的鸽子，对其脚趾残缺的发生情况以及严重程度进行记录。</p><h3 id="Part-4"><a href="#Part-4" class="headerlink" title="Part 4"></a>Part 4</h3><p>They found that human pollution likely played a part in nearly all cases of missing toes and that pigeons living in areas with higher rates of air and noise pollution tended to have fewer digits than those that lived in leafier environs.</p><p>他们发现人类污染似乎在所有丢失脚趾的案例中占据一定的原因，鸽子生活在高空中和噪音污染的环境中要比生活在多叶的环境中更容易失去脚趾。</p><h3 id="Part-5"><a href="#Part-5" class="headerlink" title="Part 5"></a>Part 5</h3><p>Perhaps most strikingly, the team noticed that toe mutilation “tended to increase with the density of hairdressers” – suggesting the birds often lose their extremities by getting them entangled in human hair.</p><p>或许最值得注意的是，他们发现这种脚趾残缺现象随理发店密度的增加而呈趋势性增多——这指出这些鸟儿的脚趾经常因为与人类的头发交缠在一起而丢失。</p><h3 id="Part-6"><a href="#Part-6" class="headerlink" title="Part 6"></a>Part 6</h3><p>The team suggested that more green spaces might benefit the population of birds seen by many city-dwellers as pests.</p><p>研究小组认为，更多的绿地可能会使许多城市居民认为是害虫的鸟类群体受益。</p><h3 id="Part-7"><a href="#Part-7" class="headerlink" title="Part 7"></a>Part 7</h3><p>But they do in fact serve a worthy purpose for science.</p><p>但事实上，它们确实为科学服务了一个有价值的目标。</p><h3 id="Part-8"><a href="#Part-8" class="headerlink" title="Part 8"></a>Part 8</h3><p>“Measuring the impacts of urban pollution on biodiversity is important to identify potential adaptations and mitigations needed for preserving wildlife even in city centres,” the team wrote.</p><p>衡量市区人口对生物多样性的影响对寻找可能的适应方式以及保护市中心等地的野生动物所需要的缓解措施来说很重要。</p><h3 id="Part-9"><a href="#Part-9" class="headerlink" title="Part 9"></a>Part 9</h3><p>The study was published in the journal Biological Conservation.</p><p>这项研究被发表在《生物保护》杂志上。</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      鸽子失去脚趾与人类脱发有关
    
    </summary>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Cook Says You Don&#39;t Need a College Degree to Be Successful</title>
    <link href="https://unshell.github.io/blog/2019/11/25/Essay-02/"/>
    <id>https://unshell.github.io/blog/2019/11/25/Essay-02/</id>
    <published>2019-11-25T03:56:45.992Z</published>
    <updated>2019-11-25T08:54:29.094Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>文章译文仅供参考</p></blockquote><h3 id="Part-1"><a href="#Part-1" class="headerlink" title="Part 1"></a>Part 1</h3><p>While a four-year college degree has become a common requirement for many jobs in the United States, even for positions that did not previously require one, Apple CEO Tim Cook is taking a different stance.  </p><p>尽管四年制大学学历已经成为美国多数工作的普遍要求，即使是以前不需要学历的一些职位。但苹果首席执行官库克对此有不同看法。</p><h3 id="Part-2"><a href="#Part-2" class="headerlink" title="Part 2"></a>Part 2</h3><p>According to Cook, there are certain in-demand skills that students may not learn in college — namely, coding.  </p><p>库克认为，有些学生在大学里可能学不到一些必需的技能–即编码。</p><h3 id="Part-3"><a href="#Part-3" class="headerlink" title="Part 3"></a>Part 3</h3><p>“And so to that end, as we’ve looked at the — sort of, the mismatch between the skills that are coming out of colleges and what the skills are that we believe we need in the future, and many other businesses do, we’ve identified coding as a very key one,” Cook said during the American Workforce Policy Advisory Board meeting on Wednesday, during which President Trump met with the board’s members, including Cook.  </p><p>库克在周三举行的美国劳动力政策咨询委员会会议上说，“因此，为了达到这个目的，正如我们已经研究过的，大学里的技能与我们认为未来需要的技能之间的不匹配，以及许多其他企业需要的技能，我们已经确定编码是非常关键的。”在会议上，特朗普总统会见了包括库克在内的董事会成员。</p><h3 id="Part-4"><a href="#Part-4" class="headerlink" title="Part 4"></a>Part 4</h3><p>Cook also added that about half of Apple’s US employment last year was made up of people who did not have a four-year degree.  </p><p>库克还补充说，苹果去年在美国雇佣的员工中，约有一半是没有四年学位的人。</p><h3 id="Part-5"><a href="#Part-5" class="headerlink" title="Part 5"></a>Part 5</h3><p>The Apple CEO also said he believes that it should be a requirement for every kid in the U.S. to have some level of coding education before they graduate high school. Apple launched its Everyone Can Code program in 2016, a curriculum designed to help students from Kindergarten to college learn coding. There are 4,000 schools in the US using Apple’s curriculum, according to Cook.  </p><p>这位苹果公司的首席执行官还说，他认为美国的每个孩子在高中毕业前都必须接受一定程度的编码教育。苹果在2016年推出了“人人都能编码”计划，该课程旨在帮助从幼儿园到大学的学生学习编码。库克表示，美国有4000所学校使用苹果的课程。</p><h3 id="Part-6"><a href="#Part-6" class="headerlink" title="Part 6"></a>Part 6</h3><p>Apple is one of several corporations that doesn’t require a college diploma for certain jobs, along with Google, IBM, Bank of America, and Hilton, according to Glassdoor.  </p><p>据“格拉斯门”（Glassdoor）报道，苹果是几家不需要大学文凭就能胜任某些工作的公司之一，还有谷歌、IBM、美国银行和希尔顿。</p><h3 id="Part-7"><a href="#Part-7" class="headerlink" title="Part 7"></a>Part 7</h3><p>While opportunities for those without a college degree are expanding, data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics published last month suggests that there’s still a sizeable discrepancy in weekly earnings between those with a college degree and those without. The median usual weekly earnings for workers with a high school diploma but no college education was $730 in 2018, while it was $1,198 for workers with a bachelor’s degree.  </p><p>尽管那些没有大学学历的人的机会正在增加，但劳工统计局上个月公布的数据表明，拥有大学学位的人和没有大学学位的人在周收入方面仍然存在很大差距。2018年，持有高中文凭但没有受过大学教育的工人的平均每周收入中值为730美元，而拥有学士学位的工人则为1198美元。</p><h3 id="Part-8"><a href="#Part-8" class="headerlink" title="Part 8"></a>Part 8</h3><p>Apple founder Steve Jobs famously started the company in his garage in 1976 after dropping out of Reed College.</p><p>1976年，苹果创始人史蒂夫·乔布斯从里德学院退学后，在他的车库里创立了这家公司。</p><h3 id="Part-9"><a href="#Part-9" class="headerlink" title="Part 9"></a>Part 9</h3><p>“So we’ve never really thought that a college degree was the thing that you had to do well,” said Cook. “We’ve always tried to expand our horizons.”  </p><p>库克说：“所以我们从来没有想过大学学位是你必须要做的事情。”“我们一直在努力拓展我们的视野。”</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      苹果CEO库克认为，成功看能力而非学历
    
    </summary>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>China&#39;s Pinduoduo Suffers $11 Billion Slump in Value After Big Loss</title>
    <link href="https://unshell.github.io/blog/2019/11/21/Essay-01/"/>
    <id>https://unshell.github.io/blog/2019/11/21/Essay-01/</id>
    <published>2019-11-21T07:16:09.015Z</published>
    <updated>2019-11-25T08:54:23.935Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>文章译文仅供参考</p></blockquote><h3 id="Part-1"><a href="#Part-1" class="headerlink" title="Part 1"></a>Part 1</h3><p>Chinese e-commerce firm Pinduoduo posted a much wider-than-expected quarterly loss as it fought bigger rivals with heavy subsidies, driving its shares down by nearly a quarter and wiping almost $11 billion off its value on Wednesday. </p><p>中国电子商务公司拼多多公布了超预期的季度亏损，因为该公司为与规模较大的竞争对手进行了激烈的补贴。在周三，其股价下跌了近四分之一，并损失了近110亿美元的市值。</p><h3 id="Part-2"><a href="#Part-2" class="headerlink" title="Part 2"></a>Part 2</h3><p>Pinduoduo’s operating costs more than doubled in the third quarter ended Sept. 30 as the company pursued a strategy of wooing wealthier consumers in big cities while maintaining its lead in less urban towns. </p><p>截至9月30日的第三季度，拼多多的运营成本增加了一倍多，因为该公司采取了一种策略，即在大城市吸引较富裕的消费者，同时在较不发达的城镇保持领先地位。</p><h3 id="Part-3"><a href="#Part-3" class="headerlink" title="Part 3"></a>Part 3</h3><p>That has pitched the four-year old startup against deep-pocketed incumbents such as Alibaba and JD.com, who are aggressively expanding in rural areas. </p><p>这让这家刚成立四年的初创公司与阿里巴巴和京东等财力雄厚的老牌企业形成了竞争，后者正在农村地区大举扩张。</p><h3 id="Part-4"><a href="#Part-4" class="headerlink" title="Part 4"></a>Part 4</h3><p>“We continued to invest in our users throughout the third quarter, and stepped our marketing up a notch from the second half of September,” Chief Executive Officer Huang Zheng said in a statement. </p><p>该公司首席执行官黄峥在一份声明中表示:“整个第三季度，我们继续投资于我们的用户，并从9月下旬开始提升我们的营销水平。”</p><h3 id="Part-5"><a href="#Part-5" class="headerlink" title="Part 5"></a>Part 5</h3><p>Huang, who owns about 45% of Pinduoduo and suffered a paper loss of about $5 billion in the stock’s post-results tumble, defended the subsidies as a worthwhile investment to help expand Pinduoduo’s user base and boost engagement in its app. </p><p>黄持有拼多多约45%的股份，在公司业绩公布后，其股价出现了约50亿美元的账面损失。黄为这些补贴辩护称，这是一项有价值的投资，有助于扩大拼多多用户基础，并提高其应用程序的参与度。</p><h3 id="Part-6"><a href="#Part-6" class="headerlink" title="Part 6"></a>Part 6</h3><p>Before Wednesday, the shares had nearly doubled this year as investors liked the company’s deep-discounting model that offers group-buying deals on grocery and generic products like toilet paper. </p><p>周三之前，该公司股价今年已上涨近一倍，因为投资者喜欢该公司的深度折扣模式，该模式提供杂货和卫生纸等日用品的团购交易。</p><h3 id="Part-7"><a href="#Part-7" class="headerlink" title="Part 7"></a>Part 7</h3><p>It also offered aggressive discounts on brand-name products throughout the year via its so-called 10 billion RMB subsidy campaign. </p><p>该公司还通过所谓的100亿元补贴活动，为名牌产品全年提供大幅折扣。</p><h3 id="Part-8"><a href="#Part-8" class="headerlink" title="Part 8"></a>Part 8</h3><p>“Exploding marketing expense is consuming the company,” said Brock Silvers, managing director at Hong Kong-based Adamas Asset Management. </p><p>总部位于香港的Adamas资产管理公司(Adamas Asset Management)董事总经理Brock Silvers表示:“爆炸式的营销费用正在吞噬公司。”</p><h3 id="Part-9"><a href="#Part-9" class="headerlink" title="Part 9"></a>Part 9</h3><p>“Investors are rejecting management’s explanation of rising costs as mere investment, and instead see a possible wobbly business model in competition with larger, better funded rivals.” </p><p>投资者拒绝接受管理层将成本上升解释为纯粹的投资，而是认为，在与规模更大、资金更充足的竞争对手的竞争中，可能会出现不稳定的商业模式。”</p><h3 id="Part-10"><a href="#Part-10" class="headerlink" title="Part 10"></a>Part 10</h3><p>The company posted a loss of 1.44 yuan per American depository share, excluding one-time items, compared with the analysts’ estimate of a 0.53 yuan per ADS loss. </p><p>该公司公布的每股美国存托股票亏损人民币1.44元，不包括一次性项目，而分析师的预估为每股美国存托股票亏损人民币0.53元。</p><h3 id="Part-11"><a href="#Part-11" class="headerlink" title="Part 11"></a>Part 11</h3><p>Still, some analysts were impressed with the results. </p><p>尽管如此，一些分析师仍对这些结果表示赞叹。</p><h3 id="Part-12"><a href="#Part-12" class="headerlink" title="Part 12"></a>Part 12</h3><p>They noted Pinduoduo’s 123% revenue growth in the quarter and a 75% surge in annual spending per active buyer this year through September versus the year-ago period. </p><p>他们指出，与去年同期相比，拼多多本季度的收入增长了123%，今年截至9月底，每位活跃买家的年支出激增了75%。</p><h3 id="Part-13"><a href="#Part-13" class="headerlink" title="Part 13"></a>Part 13</h3><p>Annual active buyers by the end of September reached 536.3 million, up 39% from a year ago, putting Pinduoduo within reach of Alibaba, which reported active users at 693 million earlier this month.<br>截至9月底，拼多多年活跃用户达到5.363亿人，较上年同期增长39%，使拼多多有望赶上阿里巴巴。阿里巴巴本月早些时候公布的活跃用户数量为6.93亿人。</p><h3 id="Part-14"><a href="#Part-14" class="headerlink" title="Part 14"></a>Part 14</h3><p>Huang talked up Pinduoduo’s rapid increase of users in bigger cities, saying they were spending well over 5,000 yuan ($710.71) a year as the company has started selling pricier products such as Dyson hair dryers and La Mer facial creams. </p><p>黄谈到拼多多在大城市用户的快速增长时，说他们每年的花费超过5000元(710.71美元)，因为公司已经开始销售价格更高的产品，比如戴森吹风机和海蓝之谜面霜。</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      中国拼多多在一场大损失后市值下降110亿美元
    
    </summary>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
